

# EMILIE TØNNESSEN

## JUNIOR FRONTEND UTVIKLER

# CONTACT

- Emilie Henriette
  Kathenes Tønnessen
- **1**2. January 1996
- +47 99 16 82 10
- @ emilie@tonnessen.com
- Bauneveien 13A1363 Høvik
- www.tonnessen.com
- www.github.com/ emilietonnessen

# ABOUTME

I am a 25-year-old student with a lot of customer experience. I am a conscientious and responsible person with a positive attitude. I have a driving force where I constantly work to improve myself as a person and in what I work with. I have a good eye for detail and see what needs to be done.

I chose Frontend Development as I am passionate about creativity and structure. I have found this possible to utilize in creating good user designs and writing semantic code. I enjoy both design and development, and am therefore very flexible. With the right guidance, Fullstack is an attractive profession to develop towards.

I am humble and have no problem acknowledging mistakes or potential for improvement, and constructive criticism is well received. I can work well independently in the home office, at the same time as I enjoy working with others. The most important thing for me is a friendly environment with development potential.

2016

# WORK EXPERIENCE

2021 - Present	Hurtigruten Group	Oslo
	Working as a Frontend Developer at Hurtigruten Group for their	

B2B team. We use React with TypeScript and libraries like Redux. For styling we use MaterialUI and JSS.

2017 - 2018 Adecco Asker og Bærum

Kindergarten Substitute

**2016 - 2017**Maxbo

Extra help on lumber dept.

Maxbo

Timber seller, 100%

2014 - 2015 Monter
Extra help and seasonal staff on lumber dept.

2013 - 2014 Risør Steinsenter Risør

Seasonal staff



### EDUCATION

2019 - 2021 Frontend Utvikling

Noroff - School of Technology and Digital Media, Nettstudier

2016 - 2019 Privatist

Sonans Oslo

2014 - 2015 VGS Elektro

Risør VGS

2012 - 2014 VGS ST Toppidrett Hest

Melsom VGS

2002 - 2012 Grunnskole

Risør barne- og ungdomsskole